however long it took
you to gain the
initially it's going
to take you an
order of a of
10 ish or so
less time to get
it back If you've
been more jacked before
if you've had bigger
muscles they come back
to their old size
If it took if
you lifted for eight
months you got a
bicep and you stopped
lifting for three months
and it looks about
the same as when
you started If you're
really careful it gets
a little bit bigger
but really it's just
back to square one
Most people think oh
my God another eight
months just to get
back to where I
started Like the gym
The truth is after
roughly about a maybe
as little as three
weeks you're have the
same size biceps that
you did in your
peak Because the degree
to which your tissue
grows if it's been
a size before especially
if it was notably
bigger than normal and
you held that around
for a months and
a it comes back
in a way that
is so fast If
you experience it yourself
it's like you don't
believe that it's happening
to you