Part one is within
about two weeks of
not training it the
first reduction in muscle
that is detectable by
modern machinery occurs So
if you don't lift
for two weeks and
we put you in
an MRI scanner or
DEXA scanner let's say
a and a you
don't lift I can't
tell you're not really
losing any yet you're
just going insane And
so me personally I'm
like to so if
I don't lift for
a I'm like God
oh my God all
my muscle's gone There
is some kind of
truth to that because
when you don't stress
your when you do
stress your they get
a bit inflamed and
they bulge up a
bit So when you're
not training for half
a week to a
your muscles look smaller
like they've lost weight
but it's really just
all water that they
lost You do one
gym session thinking like
oh my God my
biceps are gone a
and a later You
do one session at
the end of that
flex and you're like
oh my God I'm
the biggest I've ever
been I was just
delusional that whole time
because that stuff comes
back super quick After
about two weeks of
not lifting we start
to muscle but it
happens really slowly and
takes weeks and weeks
and and weeks