up that we recommend
at RP and our
app has it in
the instructions
you want let's say
you have your final
weight already picked out
Like last week you
did 20 pound dumbbells
for sets of 15
This week it's sets
of 16 with a
20 pound dumbbells What
you want to do
is you want to
do very lightweight maybe
the five pound dumbbells
for a of 12
just to get everything
moving and grooving Same
good technique same technique
you're going to use
30 seconds of a
of You pick up
the
10 or 15 pound
dumbbells and you do
a of eight reps
It's a little bit
more challenging you're feeling
your groove a bit
but your body's already
more warm your nervous
system's more active your
are more pliable You
a after that
and then you'll pick
up the you're actually
using the 20 pounders
and you'll do a
set of two to
four reps with them
just to get the
feel of that heavyweight
that you're to be
doing to acclimatize not
just your muscles and
your nervous system but
your psychology to like
okay this is the
business way that I'm
going be So 12
eight four rest another
30 seconds first working
set of whatever 16
reps you're up