If most of your
sets someone else
watching them can't tell
if you're warming up
or doing what's called
a working set like
a real set you
have a So towards
the end of all
of your sets either
the weights are slowing
down or even if
it's the same speed
to you they feel
perceptively harder You do
this this And in
a couple reps you're
like that's
what you want Every
real working set should
be You should be
approaching every real set
with just a dose
of trepidation Like oh
boy here we go
I'm to have to
try Once you have
that a set is
a group of Correct
So if I do
10 repetitions that's one
set yeah And so
your sets have to
be sufficiently heavy
Anything between roughly five
reps per set and
30 reps per set
where the last few
reps are getting close
to you not being
able to use good
technique and lift the
weights check plus