in your muscle cells
and they are to
the of
And when your generate
tension the detector machines
go oh we got
tension here And they
start saying to other
parts of the cells
like hey let's get
this growth thing started
Start it Not happening
Start it It's a
stimulus of muscle growth
There are a couple
of other mechanisms which
might slash probably have
an effect and that
a couple of them
are metabolite sequestration which
is a very fancy
way of saying the
burn You know at
the end of a
set you're like ah
the metabolites the byproducts
of training if they
accumulate to high levels
it's been shown in
tons of animal studies
and a human studies
that mechanistically they might
also tell the machinery
that grows muscle for
you again later to
hey get the muscle
growth process Another one
is the pump So
you know do a
sets of You're like
my God what's on
here baby Flash it
at some girl runs
away as usual And
the actual cell swelling
itself might play a
causal mechanistic role in
generating more muscle growth
But we know it's
probably at least 80
of the muscle growth
anyone will see is
because of those receptors
for tension