But if you're new
to the gym two
sessions a with two
to three sets per
session for your biceps
is something that's going
to cause months and
and of consistent progress
Really Can you do
more Yes Do you
have to do as
a No as a
more advanced person do
you need to do
more sets and perhaps
more sessions to get
consistently better results Yes
But for beginners who
haven't been in the
very much or at
all the minimal effective
dose is profoundly small
Which is why I
can say things like
if you work out
for 20 minutes twice
a you're to get
great gains What if
I go to the
and I do six
sets on my biceps
and I just go
to the once a
Does the distance between
the workouts in a
group have an Yes
Once a training gives
you good results But
twice a training for
the same muscle gives
you notably better results
Training three times a
versus twice Training four
times a versus three
times Training five times
a versus four times
is an
exponentially de escalating amount
of impressive differences