at the You don't
grow muscle at the
You give yourself a
to grow muscle at
the And then what
you do outside of
the gym matters So
some people train really
hard They don't eat
right They don't eat
enough protein Their sleep
is total insert bad
word here and their
stress levels are just
totally psychotic They train
hard And then week
after week after week
they're like I'm not
seeing any results Well
the are actually created
when you're resting when
you're sleeping when you're
eating nutritious food They're
stimulated in the workout
but that's just phase
one Phase two the
actual growth occurs outside
of the gym And
it occurs not at
any specific time point
like a magic window
of two hours after
the gym like that's
when all the growth
occurs That's actually when
it just starts to
go up it's four
days afterwards If you
train twice a you
train on you're growing
a of muscle on
Monday night Tuesday and
Wednesday back towards the
end of Wednesday you're
just not really growing
much more You go
back to the Thursday
you hit it hard
again