in But generally you
in the exercise science
data you'll have a
of training for sets
of roughly five reps
another group training for
sets of roughly 30
reps and their change
in muscle growth over
8 12 16 weeks
is statistically undifferentiable which
means if I de
the and you don't
know which one's which
you can't actually tell
me who trained with
higher reps or lower
reps For muscle growth
it's roughly the same
That's so We're the
same weight I'm guessing
No different weights Weight
that is for five
reps is much heavier
than a that is
for 30 OK so
I do wonder this
all time when I
go to the I
if I should be
doing I don't know
30 reps of 10
kg on my bicep
or I should be
doing 10 reps of
20 kg They're both
right answers No wrong
answers there And they
both have the same
chance of growing my
as long as the
strain that I experience
subjectively is difficult at
the end of those
sets Correct OK