a How the fuck
is that your man
If he right here
with me the boy
Turned up with my
niggas Turned up with
my bitches Turned up
with my shows Yeah
cause I got that
beat Seen some thousand
bands Came to see
me do my thing
Got a million and
one haters And they
all can kiss my
ass Turned up with
my niggas Turned up
with my bitches Turned
up with my shows
Yeah cause I got
that I'ma step ahead
and fuck up with
my clique Got backwoods
with a sock And
a bankroll full of
fiends Brought it to
the top And bitches
see me and they
don't sleep Watch out
for the fire short
I'm showing off my
moves I'm feeling cool
like I'm downstairs with
y bitches Y can't
even dream These niggas
You gon drop that
nip You know the
way I slip Them
niggas bitches pricks So
high I never rip
I keep them pussy
fresh Keep this on
wet You gon smoke
say what You get
that off your trip
Turned up with my
niggas Turned up with
my bitches Turned up
with my shows Yeah
cause I got that
beat