tonight i'm gonna let
you be your captain
you be your panda
Tonight I'm let you
be your rider Giddy
up Giddy up Giddy
up Tonight I'm let
her be fire Tonight
I'm gonna let her
bring me higher Tonight
Baby we could get
it on ye we
could get it on
ye Do you like
it boy Bon Bon
Bon Girl what wan
BonBon I love that
I love Bonbon Bon
Bon Bon Girl what
you want BonBon La
La La Na Ugh
here boy Come here
boy come here boy
come Come here boy
Come here boy Come
here boy Come here
boy boy boy
boy boy boy boy
boy boy I get
those goosebumps every time
You come around ye
You ease my mind
You make everything feel
fine Worry about those
comments I'm way too
numb ye It's way
too dumb ye I
get those goosebumps every
time I need to
hide me Throw that
to the side ye
I get those goosebumps
every time