She a baddie she
showin her panty She
shake it like jelly
Hunnid bands of Chanel
y But I'm still
shakin ass in a
deli When my bitch
gettin deady He like
him already He went
to rock but I
just went to Freddie
And I'm back in
his parlor I'm heavy
Crank me that B
while he eatin my
honey You know niggas
love bitches with money
I get a lot
Takin a spot If
you ain't cookin then
get off the pot
My name Ice but
I always stay hot
Passenger princess he pass
me his lock Baddest
lil bitch from my
block Me and baddies
be gettin along So
they always be singin
my song Steppin outside
I'ma put that shit
on 300 and then
I'll perform You know
I'ma get to the
bag All the hatin
bitches to the back
Too much to lose
so I cannot react
Them bitches be goin
outside She baddie she
showin her panty She
shake it like jelly
Hunnid bands of Chanel
y But ass in
a deli When my
bitch gettin deady He
like him already He
went to rock but
I just went to
Freddie And I'm back
in his parlor I'm
heavy Playin a snitch
and I'm showin my
Gucci PJ to Emilio
Gucci I love my
bitches