If you can't do
10K for Sweden I
don't wanna hear no
chat about numbers You
one my youngers who
play it out like
punches Tens and twenties
and hundreds tens and
twenties and thousands I
can't resist louder
on my average shouting
Soon go back to
the millions Got a
group of motherfuckers to
beat and smoke And
my day one boys
kept me close Then
I stick mine till
they take a toll
They ain't tryna get
me off the I
ain't broke I'm the
specialiest of all So
please man just be
adult And don't be
flexin in my flow
If you can't fix
me I can blow
Yo let's get this
shit off the Now
I go to Pepsi
at the home And
I ain't flexin on
them niggas cause I
be sexy at the
boat Me too it's
like I'm the size
of you But you're
major for me but
it's the size of
the boy He's the
biggest for me but
I was playing alone
When I would hit
you niggas wouldn't write
a What's life under
my under my under
my watch Never thought
you'd take me for
a kiss But don't
ask me for a
future for this All
I met is bad
comics take my fusion
Eat it use it
punch it kick off
wear it punch it
Told my job always
did it when I
jumped well Oh well
now you're stuck with
me I'm tryna hit
on the road I'm
strong Get out my
lane get out my
lane East and west
are hot but the
south on things This
here I'ma be a
house on things